echomail.com 2010-11-21

# EchoMail - E-Mail Marketing, Relationship Management, e-mail management, e-marketing, ERMS

EchoMail Inc.'s policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. EchoMail Inc.'s privacy policy adheres to the principles set forth in the "European Commission's Directive on Data Protection (Safe Harbor)" and the "Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing (CAN-SPAM) Act". This policy statement tells you how we collect information and how we use it. EchoMail Inc. follows seven core principles of privacy protection in the operation of its Web site:  

  1. Notice/Awareness of EchoMail Inc.'s information practices.
  2. Choice/Consent to provide information.
  3. Onward Transfer to a third party.
  4. Access/Participation to/in your own data.
  5. Security of the data collected.
  6. Integrity, personal information must be relevant for the purposes for which it is to be used.
  7. Enforcement/Redress through self-regulation.

**1\. NOTICE/AWARENESS**  
This policy statement sets forth EchoMail Inc. information practices concerning the type of data that is collected at EchoMail Inc.'s Web site. This policy is being placed at a link on the bottom of EchoMail Inc.'s home page, a practice that is becoming an industry standard location for Web site privacy policies.

**2\. CHOICE/CONSENT**  
The following paragraphs describe the type of information EchoMail Inc. collects and the reasons why EchoMail Inc. collects the information. By providing the information requested by EchoMail Inc.'s online forms and by continuing to use EchoMail Inc.'s Web site after having an opportunity to review EchoMail Inc.'s privacy policy, you have consented to EchoMail Inc.'s use of the information it collects as described at the point of collection or in this policy.

**User Supplied Information**  
You may be asked to supply contact information in order to receive information or materials that you request from the EchoMail.com Web site. We use contact information to send you the information you request when you submit the form. The information we collect in this manner is not used for any other purpose.

If you are using the Web site to apply for employment with EchoMail Inc., then we will use the information you provide to evaluate your application. The information you provide with your application is not used for any other purpose.

EchoMail Inc. may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) EchoMail Inc.'s rights or property or other users of the Web site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. EchoMail Inc. may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires the disclosure.

**EchoMail as an Application Service Provider:**  
In most cases, when you see an Internet form, EchoMail has been asked by the website to act as an agent for form delivery, reporting or analysis at their website. The information EchoMail processes on such a website's behalf belongs to that website and is not further used by EchoMail. EchoMail does not own the information collected and cannot use it for its own business purposes or in any way not authorized by our client.

**Your IP Address**  
EchoMail.com does not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms of use of the Web site or to protect our service, site, customers or others.

**Use of Cookies**  
EchoMail Inc. does not use cookies that contain any personally identifiable information.

**3\. ONWARD/TRANSFER**  
(Transfers to Third Parties): To disclose information to a third party, organizations must apply the notice and choice principles. Where an organization wishes to transfer information to a third party that is acting as an agent (1), it may do so if it makes sure that the third party subscribes to the safe harbor principles or is subject to the Directive or another adequacy finding. As an alternative, the organization can enter into a written agreement with such third party requiring that the third party provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the relevant principles.

**4\. ACCESS/PARTICIPATION**  
You may access the data collected by EchoMail Inc. about you by sending a request to the address listed below. If you believe that an error has been made in the accuracy of the data collected from you, EchoMail Inc. will correct such error upon adequate verification of the error and the identity of the person seeking the correction.

If you wish to access, remove or correct any personally identifying data you have supplied to EchoMail Inc. you may do so by:  

  1. Sending an e-mail request to [privacy@echomail.com](mailto:privacy@echomail.com)
  2. Sending a letter via the U.S. Mail to:  
        Privacy Officer  
        EchoMail Inc.  
        701 Concord Avenue  
        Cambridge, MA 02138

Please understand that in order to protect your privacy and security, we may also need to take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**5\. SECURITY**  
Organizations must take reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, EchoMail Inc. has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**6\. INTEGRITY OF THE DATA COLLECTED**  
Personal information must be relevant for the purposes for which it is to be used. An organization should take reasonable steps to ensure that data is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

At the present time, we DO NOT otherwise share personal information with other companies, except as is necessary in connection with our efforts to communicate with you.

**7\. ENFORCEMENT/REDRESS**  
If for some reason you believe that EchoMail Inc. has not adhered to its privacy policy, please notify us by either of the methods set forth above. EchoMail Inc. will do its best to respond to your concerns and, when appropriate, take steps to correct a problem.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using this Web site, you signify your assent to this policy statement regarding online privacy. You should also review our standard terms and conditions of use. Among other items the standard terms and conditions of use contain provisions regarding the ownership of comments and other submissions you may make to EchoMail Inc. through the Web site. If you do not agree to this policy statement as well as the terms and conditions of use, then please do not use our Web site. Your continued use of the EchoMail.com Web site following the posting of changes to this policy statement or the terms and conditions of use will mean you accept those changes. If you have any questions about this policy statement, the terms and conditions of use, the practices of this Web site, or your dealings with EchoMail Inc., you may contact us at the address given above.
